ads-securities.com 2016-03-14

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
Protecting the privacy and safeguarding the personal and financial           software to track and analyze usage and volume information including
information of our existing customers, former customers and persons          page requests, form requests and click paths. The third party may
whom visit our website is one of our highest priorities. The following       use cookies to track your web browsing behavior and may implement
statement explains how ADS Securities LLC (“ADSS”) collects, maintains       cookies on behalf of us.
and protects your information.
                                                                             All web browsers have settings that allow you to block cookies. By
By your use of any website operated by ADSS or any of our affiliates or      visiting our website with your web browser set to allow cookies, you
opening an Account with ADSS or any of our affiliate’s websites, you give    consent to our use of cookies as described above. If you choose to block
your consent to the collection and use of personal information by ADSS       cookies you may use our services, however, some functions and features
as explained in this statement.                                              may be disabled or not may not work as they were initially designed to.
COLLECTION AND RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL                                    DISCLOSURE WITH AFFILIATES
INFORMATION
                                                                             We may share your personal, financial and Account information with
We collect your personal information both directly from you and indirectly   our affiliates for business, marketing and customer service purposes,
as a result of your relationship with us. We may use the information         as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates are companies which are
collected to verify your identity, open a trading account for you (including controlled or directly or indirectly owned by us; and include financial
issuing you with an Account number and password), provide statements         service companies, such as dealers and other brokerage firms.
and trade confirmations, facilitate Account funding and withdrawals,
amongst other account and customer service related reasons. We may           To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another
also use this information to notify you of any new and existing products,    business to help us carry out certain internal functions, such as account
services and promotions that may be of interest to you.                      processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or other
                                                                             data collection activities relevant to our business. We may also provide
Most of the information we collect is provided directly by you. This         a non-affiliated third party with client information from our database,
information includes, but is not limited to, personal details, such          including your name, address, phone number, and/or e-mail address, to
as your name, address, date of birth, telephone number and e-mail            help us analyze and identify client needs, notify clients of product and
address, information required pursuant to regulatory requirements            service offerings or conduct general marketing and market research for
verifying your identity, such as a passport or other government issued       us.
photo identification, financial information such as your Account trading
details, annual income, net worth, risk capital financial information,       DISCLOSURE WITH NON-AFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES
bank account details and credit card information, and other information
such as your IP address, web browser type, operating system and your         We will not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your personal
internet service provider.                                                   information to any third party for any reason, except as described below.
Should you close your Account with us, we will retain your information,      In order to support the products and services we provide to you, we
but we will only use it to comply with our regulatory requirements and       may share your personal and Account information with third-party
to periodically contact you to notify you of new products, services and      service providers and joint marketers not affiliated with us, including
promotions we may offer from time to time.                                   but not limited to financial service institutions with whom we have joint
                                                                             marketing agreements, such as agreements to market financial services
COOKIES                                                                      or products that we jointly offer, endorse or sponsor; and companies
                                                                             under contract to perform services for us or on our behalf, such as
We use cookies and other technologies (collectively, “cookies”) to           vendors that prepare and mail statements and transaction confirmations
provide us with data we can use to improve your experience and to know       or provide data processing, computer software maintenance, and
you better. Cookies are small text files sent from various web servers       development, transaction processing and marketing services.
that may be stored on your computer. Cookies enable us to capture how
you arrived at our website, how often you visit, when you return, which      We generally require that all non-affiliated third parties to which we
pages on our website you visit, and to recognize when you are logged         provide your nonpublic information agree to keep your information
on when we receive a request from your web browser. We may link              confidential and use such information solely for the limited purpose
the information we store in cookies in order to identify information you     for which we have engaged them, or as otherwise required by law. We
submit while on our website. Cookies are readable only by us and do          also seek to ensure that these non-affiliated third parties maintain
not contain any personal, financial or Account information. We cannot        appropriate data security procedures to guard against unauthorized use
and will not gather information about other websites you have visited        of, or access to, your information.
in the past. We may share usage information about persons whom visit
our website with reputable advertising companies for the purpose of          We may disclose personal information with non-affiliated companies
targeting our banner advertisements on the internet. The information         and regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law.
collected by the advertising company through the use of these pixel tags     For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with
does not identify you personally. Additionally, we may use third party       regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with

subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our        •    Do not continue the transmission, if the SSL Certificate of
rights or property.                                                               the Website you are accessing does not belong to ADSS and
                                                                                  immediately notify ADSS;
SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION                                        •    Validate all calls, emails or other communications from ADSS
                                                                                  are genuine prior to disclosing any personal, financial or Account
We employ physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in order to             information; and
protect your personal, financial and Account information and to offer        •    Notify ADSS immediately if you believe your Account or Secure
you a safe and secure trading environment. When you open an Account               Access Website access has been compromised.
with us, you are issued a unique Account number and password, as well
a unique user id and password for the Secure Access Website.                 OPT- OUT
•    Our employees are required to maintain and protect the                  In certain instances, such as our sharing of your personal information
     confidentiality of your information and must follow established         with non-affiliated third parties, being contacted for marketing purposes
     procedures to do so.                                                    such as notifications of new products and services or market indicator
•    We limit access to your personal, financial and Account information     and research emails, you may inform us that you would like to «opt out».
     to those employees and employees of our affiliates who need             In order to opt-out, you may notify us via email at primesupport@ads-
     to know in order to conduct business, including servicing your          securities.com or contact your Account Manager that you elect to opt out
     Account. These employees will have access to your Account               of our Privacy Policy. For joint accounts, an-opt out election made by one
     number and user id. Although certain employees have the ability to      account owner will be applicable to all owners on the Account. Please
     reset your Account password and Secure Access Website password          allow approximately 30 days from our receipt of your request for your
     for you, they will not have access to your password, as they are not    instructions to become effective.
     saved in our systems.
•    We have employed adequate security measures based on                    CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT
     recognized international standards, to safeguard your information
     and protect from it from being disclosed, compromised or leaked.        In the event any material changes are made to this statement, the revised
•    Your personal, financial, and Account information, including your       Privacy Policy will be posted on our website as soon as reasonably
     credit card details (where applicable), will be disposed of or purged   practical. By your continued use of the website and/or by opening an
     from our records based on our data retention policy, which is           Account with us, you hereby agree to accept this as notice provided to
     compliance with recognized international standards.                     you.
•    We use VeriSign certificates to encrypt the information contained
     on our Secure Access Website, System and Website, including             Any dispute over this statement is subject to the terms of this statement
     the webpages used for credit card funding and online account            and our Terms of Business. If you have any questions that this statement
     application.                                                            does not address, please contact a Support representative.
You are ultimately and solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy
of your Account number and password and the Secure Access Website
user id and password. In order to better safeguard this information, we
highly recommend you the following precautions:
•    Do not disclose your Account number and password, or Secure
     Access Website user id and password to anyone;
•    Do not save your Account number and password, or Secure Access
     Website user id and password on any shared, public or private
     computer, tablet, mobile phone, or any other device;
•    Avoid using public computers at internet cafes and similar places
     whenever possible;
•    Immediately change your Account password and Secure Access
     Website password after your first log-in;
•    Change your Account password and Secure Access Website
     password regularly and whenever you believe there may have been
     a breach or when you believe a breach may occur in the future;
•    Choose strong passwords that are not easily breakable, include
     capitalized letters, numerical values and symbols and differ from
     other passwords you are using for other accounts;
•    Do not configure the save password option on the web browser you
     are using;
•    The computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other device you are using
     has security controls, such as, antivirus software;
•    Ensure that the Website you are accessing is legitimate ADSS
     Website;
                                                                                                                                                    Version 1.0 - 25/11/13
•    Make sure that the Website is changed to “https” prior to entering
     any information, such as, personal information, log-ins, passwords
     and credit card information to ensure information is encrypted
     during transmission;
